#Using Open Trivia Database API to generate questions
question_data = [{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"French is an official language in Canada.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Pluto is a planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Slovakia is a member of European Union-","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Furby was released in 1998.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"There are 86400 seconds in a day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"An eggplant is a vegetable.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the game &quot;Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code&quot;, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Books","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]